[{"answer": "It's the story of the day and even bigger than that I think is the story that Gadhafi's response to the conference in London, to President Obama's speech, is the go on the offensive not just against the rebels in the east, around Bin Jawad, and all that territory they took around the oil fields over the last few days, but also in the town of Misrata where we visited just yesterday, going on the offensive there.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Is that the story of the day?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "What we've heard in all these countries is that the people have lost the fear.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Not just Twitter but Facebook and other mediums of that type?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "What it means, Piers, is that as you well know when the coalition military activity began some 10 days ago, it occurred just as Gadhafi's forces were massing on the strategic city in the east of Benghazi where some 700,000 people were very vulnerable.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "So what does stopped in the tracks mean?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "It's really -- it's really not that confusing.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "So can you clarify it?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "We will -- as I was just getting to, we'll be providing political, humanitarian, other forms of assistance to the opposition.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Will you be arming -- will you be arming the rebels, Ambassador?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "@AmbassadorRice.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What's your -- what's your name on twitter?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Well, it certainly has dramatically changed the way that people can communicate with one another, rally one another, to common objectives.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "And what do you think of the power of Twitter in terms of what we've seen in the Middle East in particular where you have young, educated people using Twitter and other social networking means to spread the message from these countries in the way they perhaps wouldn't have been able to 10, 15 years ago?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "It's extremely humbling to see how quickly the velocity of the service, how it's taken off.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams that you would have that kind of spread?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "So it's always been focused on the recipient.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Was that part of the thinking?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Well, it means that -- for example, in Egypt -- so when I go to Tahrir Square, as you know I did during the protests, and I see a thug sent by Mubarak, one of these plainclothes policemen carrying this big club with nails embedded in it, then you know I don't wait to see what happens, I don't wait for -- until my next column.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "How dramatically has this changed your working practice?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Which is amazingly powerful firsthand immediate testimony, isn't it?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "It was one of our co-workers, Noah Glass.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Whose idea was it?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Could you?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, actually that has come up a few times when I'm in some very dicey position, and I tweet.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "The bosses or Twitter?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "It is very much so.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Because I've noticed it's a mixture of amusing stuff about you and your life, but primarily it's a fantastic business tool, isn't it?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- right now I have about 2.2 million followers.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "How vast is your audience at the moment?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I don't think she's going to actually take over the presidency if she gets more followers than Obama.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Does it show power and influence, the total?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, you could.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "You become almost a -- in perpetuity publicist, don't you?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know what a bad use it, because I have had only very, very good response to my tweets.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What is a bad use of Twitter, particularly for famous people?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I'm a newbie, yes.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "While you're still -- are you still new to it?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Pierogi.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Because you're of Polish descent, what is your favorite Polish dish that you like to cook?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Pierogi?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "It's a dumpling.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "And what is Pierogi?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "It's tomorrow.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "That's tomorrow, right?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "Well, I just got a whole lot of tweets from people saying -- I'm sure they're dictating the requests of their child or something, asking how difficult is it, it is very easy.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "What's the persuasive element for you?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Should you drink and tweet?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "That was a very proud Twitter moment for me, yes.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Alyssa, this was a rather curious way to track your follower account up, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Definitely, definitely.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Forget business for a moment, in terms of raising awareness of issues, charitable causes?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "ILANO: No.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Did you have any -- any qualms about doing that?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "We're all Twits.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "We're all Twits, really, aren't we?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Actually, early on I didn't think celebrities would want to use Twitter because I thought for exactly that reason, that part of their allure was that you couldn't get close to them.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "About stars?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Here's a good one.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "I want to see -- Martha, you got any good Tweets?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Well, every mayor was struggling in this area.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "And in contrast to poor old Mayor Bloomberg, who was getting booted all around New York by the media because he had the gall to spend 48 hours without solving it, which in Britain would have taken three years -- you were getting all the praise because you hit the Twitter and you were just talking directly to people trapped in the snow, weren't you?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "I got on in March -- May of '09.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "When did you realize this was going to be a really effective tool for you?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Is that what you want to see happen?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "It's amazing what people are doing with it.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Pretty extraordinary, isn't it?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I don't know if it's practical there.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Would you like to see the president being more pro- active on Twitter himself, actually doing what you do?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think that leaders need to be accessible.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "What do you think about the role of Twitter in creating talented leaders in U.S. politics?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "ILANO: I don't know about baby pictures, because then that becomes a security issue.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "When you have your baby, will you be putting the first baby pictures proudly up on your Twitter, Tweeting to the world?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "That's the definition of obsessive junkie, isn't it?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Yeah, I do.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "You see it as a really great business tool, don't you?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "We've talked about this before.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Who wants to see that all way?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "Well, it's a public medium.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Can you get a little bit too fresh on Twitter?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Square.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "I can swipe your card right here.", "docId": "110329pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "What do I do?", "qSentId": 699}]